Well, we started this week with Amecha,
What's up, you're doing the sensible championship that's been going on for a long time.
So far, Moeka-chan is at the bottom of all of them?
For now,
Out!
Yes!
Okay, I'm already a lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering lumbering
I'd like to give Moeka a chance here.
Here's an emergency plan!
Mr. Suzuki always loves milk!
I love it!
7-Eleven, Famimarose, and the well-known Oishii Milk.
We'd like you to pull milk from these four.
I'll do my best!
I love milk, I drink it every day.
Then, if you can't do this...
You can't call yourself a milk lover.
Why not, I drink it every day.
Then don't drink milk.
Why not?
Next.
It's so heavy!
The "heavy" part of the song is also a white robbery!
I know the lyrics say milk, but...
But that part is different.
That part is all Kojima.
Then he's in here.
I hate milk, Kojima-san!
I'll take the person who did it wrong.
I'll take this on your notation.
But I love it. I'm sure you can guess this.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
Oh, no.
You drank too much.You drink too much.
From now on...
Pretty for you
Let's make it happen with you
Another mind
Tell me now
If it's words, I don't need them anymore
It's up now, it's up now
You and me so amazing
Come on
I don't know. That's why...
Mr. Suzuki.
He's wearing a blindfold and earphones.
I'd like to make Mayuka drink milk.
This time, I'd like to give her...
It's a special one.
Ta-da!
Coffee milk!
If you haven't noticed...
You're in big trouble.
Well, Mai-Ito-chan...
Yes, I'd like you to drink this first.
Yes, you just have to remember this, right?
Yes, that's all you need to remember.
Wait.
Yes, sir.
Do you understand?
Not at all.
Yes, sir.
What do you mean?
Did you remember?
Yes. Do you think I'm insensitive?
What?
If Moe-kan said this.
Can I call you a sensitive woman now?Can I call myself a sensitive onna now?
Sure.
Coffee milk, right?
No, sir.
But...
It's good milk. Where's the coffee?
Coffee milk! It's coffee.
No one calls it coffee.
But the product is.
It's "good milk"!
How insensitive do you think I am?
I'd like you to try this milk.
Are you sure you can tell?
I'll do my best. I drink milk all the time.
Can you do it?
Then, let's get started.
This way, sir.
Ta-da!
I'll put it in.
If I say any more, I'll get all busty.
Dunkiri Hotel
I got a hint.
A hint? Is that a hint?
Dankiri Hint
Dandori Hotel
Can I have a drink?
Please let me drink.
Please don't get excited
Please don't let me be invisible
I want to have a good time with you
Here you are, Smokey!
Yes, sir.
Smell, touch, feel...
Mmm-hmm.
Looks delicious.
Bon appétit!Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.
Wow, it's delicious.
Oh, it's so good.
This is so good.
Oh, I found it.
I love it.
Yeah.
But you know, I heard about one.
I haven't even seen it. I haven't even drunk it.
Okay, okay.
It's good.
Is it good?
I remember.
Let's get you back on your feet.
Can you guess?
In any order is fine.
Okay? Let's get started.
I drink this a lot.
I don't know, I just don't feel like this one.
Can I try one of these?
No, not at all.
It's not this one!
No?
No!
So you're declaring this one out?
You can't change it now.
How is it different from before?
I don't know. It smells different, tastes different.
There's more of a smell to it.
I like it when it smells really thick.
It was a lot like that before.
It's different.
Compared to before...
So this is different.
So that's your final answer?So is it a final answer?
Final answer!
Mayuka
Correct!
Not at all.
Okay, next.
But...
It tastes so much like the package.
The packaging?
You bought it... in my imagination.
So I'm going to finish it.
I'll have a Famima.
Bon appétit!
But it looks really, really...
Too rich?
It's the same!
Bon appétit!
It's not the same.
It's different.
No, it's not.
I don't know how to say this.
It's so uniform.
I don't know how to say it.
It's... it's... it's... it's... it's uniform.
Uniformity.
It smells different, but...
If you don't do this, it's all the same.
It looks the same, but it's not.
But it's not the same.
This is definitely not the same.
I'm sure of it.
Handal Arthur.
I can't go back.
I'm really okay now.
No more of this mind games.
I like the way you're thinking.I like to start with a good thought.
No, sir.
Let me guess!
Yeah!
200 points, right?
I should probably guess.
But I want to drink all of them, so I'll take this one.
This one's probably not right.
Okay, this one.
Okay?
I don't think this one's right.
I have to drink it.
Then I'll drink it.
Bon appétit.
Oh!
Sway.
I want to drink it so bad!
Wait a minute.
No, no, no.
How's it taste?
It's rich.
It's delicious.
You have to try it.
I want some.
Please, please, please, please.
Please?
Yeah, all of it, please.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You can't ask Yuzu. It's cheating.
No, no, no, no. It's not cheating.
No, no, no, no.
Change of rules!
No, no, no, no. Don't be so smug.
If you want to prove your sensitivities.
I want you to be serious now.
Remember your first taste.Remember that first taste.
Go for it.
No, this isn't it.
No?
Then let's do that.
Final answer.
Final answer, this is different.
Mr. Suzuki
Correct! Yes! I'm so happy!
This is Ira's recommendation!
Oh!
Delicious!
But you know what, Ira, what you said earlier kinda scared me a little.
You know, just a little bit.
Before we started.
Ira Lunch... he said he only buys this, this and this.
Ira likes it, right?
When you say you like her, this is already erased, right?
That's right.
This is so delicious.
Oh, I found it.
I like this a lot.
I like it.
Mm-hm. - Mm-hm.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I found myself wanting to get angry at Ayana.
It was me, wasn't it?
I thought for a while that I had to make a decision based on taste.
That's why you said that in the end.
Yes, it did cross my mind.
It proves that Mr. Suzuki is great!
Yes, that's great!Yay, that's good.
I've made up a little ground, for a change.
That's good.
Good, good, good.
Well, Ayana...
Ayana had a little bit of a mishap.
Ayana, after you said you'd never speak again...
Next, I said...
Ayana said, "You like this, don't you?
I think I was a little insensitive.
She's the current winner, though, isn't she?
That's right.
That's the point, isn't it?
I look forward to working with you.
Next game.
Shall we go?
I'm looking forward to it.
Eight correct guesses in a row.
Yay!
I want to go to the game.
Just make sure you get this one right first.
You can go home.
Oh, really?
It's a real bummer.
Are you sure about this?
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm good.
I want to go home.
This is really good.
I wonder if it's gonna grow.
Oh, this is seriously good.